{
    "question": "C. Should not    D. Should\r\n21.\r\nMy mom says I..... play more with my pet when I am bored.\r\nA Has to\r\nB. Have to\r\nC. Must\r\nD. Should\r\nLast weekend I and my classmates went to the countryside to have a picnic. Befo\r\neaving, we made some sandwiches for lunch. We left quite early to avoid the trat\r\nam\r\nAfter driving for two hours, we arrived at a very nice place. It was near a river\r\nsome big trees around it. The driver parked the car under the tree. Seeing the e\r\nin cool water of the river, my friends and I decided to swim. After having\r\nmox the scenery We saw some beautiful\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>21. D (should)</p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu^^</p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "buatlah-sebuah-short-massage-dengan-tema-terserahhh-pliss-ja-513",
            "question": "Buatlah sebuah short massage, dengan tema terserahhh.... \r\n\r\npliss jawabbb....\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Random Guy : Hi, do you like coffee?</p><p>Her Crush : Ah! yes, so you like coffee to?</p><p>Random Guy : Ya, i like coffee to.</p><p>\"Here is your coffee with milk sir&#039;</p><p>Random Guy : Ah! thanks.</p><p>Her Crush : So you like milk?</p><p>Random Guy : Yes, and you?</p><p>Her Crush : No, that give me some gas.</p><p>Random Guy : Okay</p><p>...........</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "read-the-dialog-and-answer-the-questions-number-2-to-4-onci-do-y-402",
            "question": "Read the dialog and answer the questions number 2 to 4.    Onci\r\nDo you know where Clara is?\r\nDafa She is in our school library. She went there with Ms. Nina, our school librarian, a few\r\nminutes ago\r\nOnci\r\nDafa\r\nWhat does she do in the library?\r\nShe helps Ms. Nina and Mr. Eko to check and arrange the books. She usually also helps the\r\nlibrary visitors to find some books. She always is in the library on Monday and Wednesday.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Kak pertanyaannya mana? ga bisa jawab</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bahasa-indonesia-1-kalimat-majemuk-dalam-teks-ulasan-dibagi-menj-375",
            "question": "BAHASA INDONESIA    1. Kalimat majemuk dalam teks ulasan dibagi menjadi dua salah satunya adalah...\r\na. kalimat majemuk setara\r\nb. kalimat majemuk bertingkat\r\nc. kalimat penghubung\r\nd. kalimat kompleks\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Yaitu, kalimat majemuk yang polanya tidak sederajat (bertingkat). ... teknik membaca yang dianggap sebagai salah satu teknik membaca</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "how-do-you-speak-these-named-asiti-breny-cbudi-883",
            "question": "How do you speak these named?\r\n a.SITI\r\n b.RENY\r\n c.BUDI",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>c</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>gh86fiyfihvyixgj8ycygij8</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "always-j-activity-1-get-up-at-am-2-aake-his-bed-3-take-a-ba-145",
            "question": "Always    J\r\n\u2713\r\nActivity\r\n1. get up at AM\r\n2. aake his bed\r\n3 take a bath\r\n+ har's hrcaktast\r\n5. catch the bus to school\r\n6. haiclunch at school\r\nplas basketball in the aftemoon\r\n8. plas antes\r\n9. study in the evening\r\n10. go to bed at 9 PX\r\n1. How does he go to school?\r\n2. Does he like playing games?\r\n3. Where does probably he always have breakfast?\r\n4. Here are Rick's routines.\r\nThe closest meaning of the underlined word is\r\non we probably find the notice?\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. How does he go to School </p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "rio-hello-dhika-what-time-do-you-usually-go-to-school-dhika-i-137",
            "question": "Rio Hello, Dhika. What time do you usually go to school?    Dhika :I go to school at six o'clock\r\nRio : Six o'clock? How do you go to school?\r\nDhika : I go to school by school bus\r\nRio Now. What kinds of things do you take to school?\r\nDhika : I usually take my backpack and books\r\nRio : okay. What is the first thing you do when you arrive at school?\r\nDhika we always greet our teachers and start our class with prayer\r\nRio : why do you usually study at school on Monday?\r\nDhika : we study English, civics, art and math\r\nRio : okay, where do you usually eat for lunch? Do you have lunchroom, canteen or cafeteria?\r\nDhika yes, there is canteen in my school\r\nRio now, what time do you usually go home?\r\nDhika : we sometimes go home at 3 o'clock\r\n1. What time does Dhika go to school?\r\nA. At six o'clock\r\nB. At seven o'clock\r\nC. At eight o'clock\r\nD. At a half six o'clock\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>A. at six a clock</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p> semangat belajar nya ! </p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>A. At six o&#039;clock</p><p></p><p>thanks</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "kan-tadi-saya-dikirimi-temen-tc-sebut-nama-nah-ini-cara-jawabn-456",
            "question": "Kan tadi saya dikirimi temen \"tc sebut nama \" nah ini cara jawabnya gimana ya?\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>tc=test contact</p><p></p><p>itu biasanya buat ngetes nomornya masih aktif atau tidak ya jawab aja nama mu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "savage-love-laxed-siren-beat-jason-derulo-jawsh-685-if-i-wok-145",
            "question": "Savage Love (Laxed - Siren Beat)    Jason Derulo, Jawsh 685\r\nIf I woke up without ya\r\nI don't know what I would do\r\nThought I could be single forever\r\n'Til I met you\r\nUsually don't be fallin', be fallin'\r\n, fallin' fast\r\nYou got a way of keeping me comin' back to\r\nback\r\nI just found out, the only reason that you lovin'\r\nBaby I know she creepin', I feel it in the air\r\nEvery night and every day\r\nI try to make you stay\r\nBut your Savage love\r\nDid somebody, did somebody\r\nBreak your heart?\r\nLookin' like an angel\r\nBut your savage love\r\nWhen you kiss me I know you don't give two\r\nf**ks\r\nbut I still want that ...\r\nme\r\nWas to get back at your ex-lover but before you\r\nleave Usually I would never, would never even\r\ncare\r\n48. What happen if the singer wakes up without his girl?\r\nA. He will be lazy to wake up\r\nB. He could be single forever\r\nC. He usually doesn't fall fast\r\nD. He doesn't know what will he do\r\n49. What is the only reason the girl loves the singer?\r\nA. To take money and fame\r\nB. To get back to her ex-lover\r\nC. To know that he is creeping\r\nD. To make him feel it in the air\r\n50.. Why does the girl have a savage love?\r\nA. She loves to play victim\r\nB. The man doesn't really care\r\nC. Someone broke the girl's heart\r\nD. They are not mean to each other.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>48. D. He doesn&#039;t know what will he do</p><p>49. C. To know that he is creeping</p><p>50. C. Someone broke the girl&#039;s heart</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "48. D<br>49. D<br>50. C<br>I think it\u2019s not correct answer",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "what-does-the-text-tell-us-about-the-text-tells-about-462",
            "question": "What does the text tell us about? the text tells about ... .",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:my mom bought a new bag for me </strong></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:EZ!</strong></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "our-scholl-is-very-we-can-play-and-do-many-activities-here-we-l-659",
            "question": "Our scholl is very we can play and do many activities here . we love it very mu h\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>sekolah kami sangat kami bisa bermain dan melakukan banyak kegiatan di sini. kami sangat menyukainya</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu </p><p>                                </p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}